(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Hello, welcome to my 3D live!
Mini 3D live, actually!
Happy two years!
I kind of want to go somewhere really nice.
Look at the sky.
Look at how beautiful the weather is.
I wouldn't call this weather.
Look at this beautiful weather.
I want to—I want to go somewhere nice.
Where should I go?
Oh!
What's there? Wait.
Let me get—let me get closer.
Huh?
Ah!
Ah! It's a heli!
It's a heli! We have a helicopter!
Wait.
Wait, I want to—I want to—
I want to ride a heli!
This is like my 3D showcase, actually.
I remember that I rode a heli once.
Whoa!
We're actually flying!
Wait, what?
Oh my god, we're flying!
We're flying!
え、すごい！
Eh, amazing!
え、we're flying, chat! Whoa!
Eh, we're flying, chat! Whoa!
Let me get out of here.
I can't get out of here.
Wait, now I can.
Oh! Whoa! Bye-bye!
Bye-bye, heli!
Whoa, that was so cool.
Yeah, and that's a grand entrance, isn't it?
Be-fitting for me, the best agent in the world.
Huh?
What are you looking at?
You're late to your mission, Zekataries!
I know you're so—
You were supposed to be waiting for me at the stage.
And now, to do your mission!
And to greet me once I get off the helicopter.
But now what are you doing?
You're doing nothing but waving a light stick!
Is this what you were born to do?
I'm so aggressive.
Wait, watch this, watch this, okay? Watch this.
Whoo! Guess who's here!
Zekataries!
Oh!
Hello! Hello!
Why don't you guys say something? Hello! Hello!
You guys are lifeless.
I'm the same.
Sometimes I feel lifeless too.
Okay, what about—
What about—what about this part?
Watch this.
Whoo! Isn't the stage beautiful?
I was going to show—show you out the stage earlier, but I forgot.
I have two-second memory, so...
Look at the beautiful skies.
I wanted something like, um, really magical.
Something like starry night, langit...
Something like starry night, the sky...
Enggak tahu, langit.
I don't know, the sky.
Like anything related to gastronomy—wait, astronomy!
Astronomy! Not gastronomy.
That's stomach, holy crap.
Astronomy. Look!
There's a shooting star!
There's a shooting star! Make a wish.
Make a wish.
What did you make a wish?
You guys have to make a wish.
Oh! What do you think about this one?
Do you know what it says there?
Can you find something? Can you guys tell me what it says?
Yes!
It—it says Zeta on the stage.
You know, because...
Zeta is—Zeta is the best thing that could ever, ever happen—
What's wrong with my speech?
...that could ever happen in your life.
Oh, wait, look at this one.
Are you guys ready? Sorry.
I was like trying to talk while I maneuver through this thing.
I'm very new to VR, so...
This is very, very difficult for me.
I am entering a whole new world, you know?
But yeah!
I was thinking, since it's our two-year anniversary...
...on this channel, I was thinking why not celebrate...
...me being two years old?
I'm just kidding, so young.
Me being—
I wouldn't say—
If I've been streaming for two years,
does that mean I'm old now?
Like, is two years old old?
Like, hello?
Oh! Hello, I'm back chat.
I know you missed my face. I know you missed my face.
And I was like, you guys are probably like...
"Where's Zeta? I don't want to see the stage", like...
How dare you!
Huh? Huh?
This stage was made with lots of love and care.
How dare you not want to see the stage.
Anyways... I'll show you around.
As you guys can see, you are in the back...
...waving... waving that lightstick...
...with no single thought in your head.
Just like me.
If you want to get closer, you might notice that I have no single thought.
Oh, I look like I have a mohawk here.
Jamet banget.
So tacky.
Jamet banget kalau kayak gini.
It looks so tacky if it's like this.
Anjay!
Holy cow!
Whoo! Okay, I'm not used to holding a selfie stick, so if...
...if it... oh! Well, if it gets turned around, then I'm sorry.
Well, I have a bunch of things that I wanted to show you. Watch this, okay?
(Humming)
Wait... whoa!
Wait... (laughs)
You probably... you probably didn't know what just happened.
Ah, I'm tired. I want to lie down.
I want to lie down.
Okay, break time's over.
Okay, watch this. I have...
Bwa bwa bwa bwa bwa... bwa bwa bwa bwa bwa...
Watch this. Chipi chipi chapa chapa...
I've always wanted to rap in this stage made just for me, you know?
I thought it would be cool. I'm just like, "yeah".
Yo, yo, yo, mic check one, two.
I'm the next rapper in town. What was my rapper name again?
DJ... DJ V-V-V... DJ V-7 or something?
I don't remember to be honest.
Damn, I have a two-second memory like a goldfish.
Oh, wait! With a mic too! I should have done it with a mic.
Yo, yo, yo! Yo, yo, yo!
Watch me... watch me hit you with this mic!
(Hitting noises)
Oh... this might be a little bit more tame.
I won't... I won't hit you anymore, okay? I won't hit you anymore.
Ready for the surprise? Ready for the surprise?
I won't hit you anymore.
One evil thought.
It's a cat! What do you think?
(Humming "Cat Dance" tune)
How does the cat dance go again?
(Humming)
Yeah, it's a cat! Do you like it?
I'm going to do a 360 for you. 360 no scope. Bye-bye!
Spin!
Wait, I can actually do spinning in real time now. Wait.
Wait, I can... oh, I'm so dizzy. I'm so motion sick.
Thank you very much, I'm so motion sick.
Why did you do that to me? Why did you make me motion sick?
You know that I'm prone to motion sickness! Why did you do...?
This is probably the most motion sick inducing VR concert...
Not... Okay, I should stop calling it a concert.
It's not a concert. It's more like a fun free talk, zatsu, you know? Zatsu?
Like a fun segment. So, free talk? I would consider it free talk.
We are doing a lot of free talking here and a lot of...
...camera smashing, motion sick inducing stuff.
Would you like to keep me...
Would you like for me to keep the cat ears on or not?
Because I feel like you guys would appreciate my hair more.
Since my hair already looks like the ears anyway, so I don't think we need it.
We don't need it.
Look, pretty much the same.
Okay, oh no! I literally just admitted... No, it's not the same.
That's hair, okay? Shut up, furries.
This is hair. You can't just equate anything remotely...
...hair-like to animals.
I have a guest!
I have a guest on this special anniversary stream, and that is...
#2ETAnniv
Bazo!
What do you think?
Is it cute?
Pretty cute, right?
Pwa pwa pwa... pwa pwa pwa pwa.
So cute. Wait, if I...
if I bend over, maybe you'll be able to see better.
This is Bazo. Isn't he so cute?
Wait, come closer.
Wait, that's not me.
What the?
This one, this way?
Yeah. What you doing, baby girl?
Yeah, this is Bazo. Very cute.
I know you guys love Bazo more than me sometimes.
Um, what else, what else?
Oh, I have my usual emote.
If you remember, type this in chat.
My usual emote. Wait, watch this. Hehehe...
Hehehe. It's the :w:, :w:. My usual emote.
Um, I have a really sad, sad emote as well.
Watch this.
Watch this, okay?
Prep- be prepared to be sad, everyone.
Be prepared to... be prepared to sad.
What is wrong with my English today?
Siap-siap nangis. Lihat ini, oke?
Get ready to cry. Look at this, okay?
Uwaaa... uwaaa...
It's such a tragic day today.
Zeta turned 2 years old.
Two today...
Wait, watch this. I can go even sadder.
Uwaaa... Please! No!
Don't take my...
don't take my... what is it called?
Don't take my expired food away. No!
Don't take my coffee away.
What about this? Hmm... what do you guys think?
Tu tu ru tu ru tu ru...
Hah!
Hah! You eat veggies?
You are so disgusting! Just kidding.
And this one...
Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait!
The thing is, with...
with this chibi body, I can't really like...
my movement is very limited.
But, you know, I can still move around
and have fun with you guys.
So I don't think that's too much
of a problem, you know?
Hehehe! Hehehe! This is a happy, happy one.
But watch this.
へっ？なんでそんなことできるの？
Heh? How can you do that?
なんでそんなことできないの？はっ？
Why can't you do that? Huh?
Why can't you even do that?
That's just such a simple thing.
Why can't you just wash the dishes?
This is smug. This is smug Gaki Zeta.
Sorry, I keep hitting the mic,
you're probably gonna die.
Um, yeah, this is Gaki Zeta, you know?
I think you guys might like Gaki Zeta.
Hmm... Wait, give me one second.
Okay, I had to adjust the mic a little bit, but...
Watch this.
Whoo! キラキラ！キラキラ！
Whoo! Sparkle sparkle! Sparkle sparkle!
And this one.
You guys already seen this one, but...
me when I don't get my daily intake of coffee.
Hah! Where's my caffeine?
Okay, well... I am excited to show you guys
um, what we have in store today.
I was thinking we can do a little bit of free talk
and maybe some songs in between, you know?
You know, what do you guys think?
Um, I kind of want to like... um, I don't know,
I have no thoughts.
I... the thing is I don't... I just...
the thing is I just don't think.
I'm just gonna chill with you guys today
and do whatever feels best.
If I... if I wanted to do a backflip, then I would...
What about this?
This is cute.
This one is cute.
Pee!
Ha!
You!
This one's cute.
Okay!
Well...
I will show you...
I will show you.
Ah...
Let's get back into position.
Okay, okay.
Okay...
Let's get back into position.
And...
I want you guys to have fun with me, okay?
This is nothing serious,
so please, let's all just like have fun together, you know?
Have fun together.
Enjoy these moments together.
And...
yeah, if you guys know the song, we can sing along,
but if you don't, that's fine too.
Just...
if you don't...
if you don't,
you can just sit there and wave the... wave the lightsticks.
You can just sit there and wave the lightsticks.
Okay!
Sign Wa B
サインはB
B-Komachi
Sign Wa B
Sign Is B
B-Komachi
あなたのアイドル
I'm your idol!
サインはB！
The sign is B!
チュッ！
Mwah!
ようやく会えたね
We finally met!
嬉しいね
I'm so happy!
待ち遠しくて足をバタバタしながら
I was so eager I was kicking my feet!
今日楽しみで
Looking forward to today,
寝れなかったよ
I couldn't sleep!
緊張なんかしてる場合じゃない
This is no time to be nervous!
一分一秒無駄になんてできないさ
We can't waste even a single second!
さあ始めましょう
So, let's get started!
君も君も君もお待たせさま！
To you, and you, and you, thanks for waiting!
手を鳴らせ
Clap your hands!
いらっしゃいませ
Welcome!
好きが詰める場所へようこそ
Welcome to the place filled with love!
日常はクローゼットの中
Leave your daily life in the closet!
ここに来たなら踊らにゃ損損
Since you're here, it's a waste not to dance!
下界の悩みは関係ない
Worldly troubles don't matter!
箱が大きい小さいとか気にしない
I don't care if the venue is big or small!
ちゃんと見えてる
I can clearly see
君のサイリウム
your lightstick!
今はボロボロバカみたいだろな
Right now I probably look like a total mess!
小さら小さい才能だけど
I only have a tiny bit of talent, but...
私を推してくれるのなら
if you support me...
極レスをあげる
I'll give you my best fan service!
あなたのアイドル
I'm your idol!
サインはB！
The sign is B!
チュッ！
Mwah!
いつか俺が育てたって
I want you to brag...
近い将来自慢してほしいよ
in the near future, that you were the one who raised me!
期待させたい
I want to make you look forward to it!
君と君と今を楽しまなきゃ
We have to enjoy the moment with you and you!
引きこもりも
Shut-ins and
人見知りも
shy people,
普段と違う顔見せてよ
show me a face different from usual!
みんな今日どう調子どうだい
How are you all doing today?
なりふり構わず
Don't worry about how you look,
そうそうそう
that's it, that's it!
左見右笑いとか関係ない
It doesn't matter if people laugh at you!
マイキャラとかとか気にしない
I don't care about your persona or anything!
成長中よ
I'm still growing!
君のサイリウム
(I see) your lightstick!
たとえ世界が私を拒んで
Even if the world rejects me...
一人ぼっちを感じたとしても
and I feel all alone...
あなたが味方でいてくれたら
if you're on my side...
怖いものはないよ
there's nothing to be afraid of!
見せよう
Let's show them!
今から始まる
Starting now,
君との物語が
the story between you and me!
なんて素晴らしい景色だ
What a wonderful sight!
下界の悩みは関係ない
Worldly troubles don't matter!
箱が大きい小さいとか気にしない
I don't care if the venue is big or small!
ちゃんと見えてる
I can clearly see
君のサイリウム
your lightstick!
今はボロボロバカみたいだろな
Right now I probably look like a total mess!
小さら小さい才能だけど
I only have a tiny bit of talent, but...
私を推してくれるのなら
if you support me...
あなたが味方でいてくれたら
if you're on my side...
極レスをあげる
I'll give you my best fan service!
あなたのアイドル
I'm your idol!
サインはB！
The sign is B!
チュッ！
Mwah!
Yay!
How was it?
Did you wave your lightsticks around?
Did you?
I saw you in the audience and you weren't waving your lightsticks,
you were...
you were just staying still.
Losers. Just kidding.
Um, so next song, so next song is something, something you guys might really like.
Hehehe. What do you think it is?
I wanted something really like groovy, really like slow,
cause lately I've been really into like, like sweet but like slow songs, you know?
Um... what if I bring a friend with me?
What do you guys think? Should I bring...
...should I bring a friend with me? (Struggling sounds) Hahaha!
I'm going to bring him along as well.
バゾのこと好き？
Do you like Bazo?
バゾ好き？
バゾ好き？ん？
Do you like Bazo? Hmm?
好きはダメだよ。
You can't like him.
You can't like Bazo. Bazo's mine.
He's my slave forever. You can't like him.
Well, and on that note,
I have a song related to a person or someone that you can't like, okay?
So let's go!
Next song!
好きになっちゃダメな人
The person you shouldn't fall in love with
負けじゃん 勝てるわけないじゃん
I've lost already, haven't I? There's no way I can win
最初から分かってた
I knew it from the start
あなたは あなたは
That you are, you are
好きになっちゃダメな人
The person you shouldn't fall in love with
あなたの「好き」ってどんな「好き」？
What kind of 'like' is your 'like'?
多分私と違う「好き」
It's probably a different 'like' from mine
「可愛い」だなんて言葉でごまかさないで
Don't try to gloss it over with words like 'cute'
大事にされてること、は痛いほど分かるけれど
I know you treasure me, so much it hurts
何かが足りない 違う そうじゃない
Something's missing, it's different, that's not it
気持ちが死にたい mm-mm-mm
My feelings want to die, mm-mm-mm
私が大きくなったよ
I've grown up, you know
背伸びしたら届きそうな
If I stretch on my tiptoes, I could almost reach
あなたの唇
Your lips
もう子供扱いしないでよ
Stop treating me like a child already
ほらまた頭くしゃって
See, you're ruffling my hair again
くしゃってする
Ruffling it like that
好きになっちゃダメな人
The person you shouldn't fall in love with
負けじゃん 勝てるわけないじゃん
I've lost already, haven't I? There's no way I can win
そのずるい笑顔に 飲み込まれてゆく
I'm being swallowed up by that unfair smile of yours
好きになっちゃダメな人
The person you shouldn't fall in love with
こんなのってないじゃん
This is so unfair, isn't it?
最初から分かってた
I knew it from the start
あなたは あなたは
That you are, you are
好きになっちゃダメな人
The person you shouldn't fall in love with
想いに気づくタイミングは
The times to realize my feelings
たくさんあったはずなのに
There must have been so many of them
私可愛くないほど 素直じゃない
I'm not honest enough to be cute
このまま消えたい mm-mm-mm
I just want to disappear like this, mm-mm-mm
気持ちが膨れ上がるたび
Every time my feelings swell up
バレるのが悔しくて
It's frustrating that they'll be found out
隠した横顔
So I hide my profile
好きでいさせて 一人なの？
Let me keep loving you, am I all alone?
そうだと知ってしまって 涙が出る
Knowing that's the case makes the tears fall
好きにならないほうが無理じゃん
It's impossible not to fall for you, isn't it?
かなうわけないじゃん
There's no way it'll come true
ずっと心の中 住みついている
You've been living inside my heart all along
好きにならないほうが無理じゃん
It's impossible not to fall for you, isn't it?
どうしようもないじゃん
I can't help it, can I?
最初から決まってた
It was decided from the start
あなたは あなたは
That you are, you are
多分きっと運命の人
Probably, surely, my person of destiny
特別だと思う やっぱり
I think you're special, after all
あなたの一挙手一投足が
Every move you make
気になって 気になって
Is on my mind, so much
好きになっちゃダメな人
The person you shouldn't fall in love with
負けじゃん 勝てるわけないじゃん
I've lost already, haven't I? There's no way I can win
そのずるい笑顔に 飲み込まれてゆく
I'm being swallowed up by that unfair smile of yours
好きになっちゃダメな人
The person you shouldn't fall in love with
こんなのってないじゃん
This is so unfair, isn't it?
最初から分かってた
I knew it from the start
あなたは あなたは
That you are, you are
好きになっちゃダメな人
The person you shouldn't fall in love with
Hi!
Yay!
See, I told you it was groovy, right?
Now, I'm ready to sing the next song.
Are you ready? Are you ready?
I want to sing, oh...
I want to sing, um...
Ah, ini gimana sih kameramennya?
Ah, what's with the cameraman?
Gimana sih?
What's going on?
Mutar-mutar gak jelas.
Spinning around aimlessly.
Hey, di sini, di sini!
Hey, over here, over here!
Gini gini gini.
Like this, this, this.
Gini, di sini. Di sini.
Like this, over here. Over here.
Di sini, di sini. Bukan di sana.
Over here, over here. Not over there.
Sudahlah, whatever.
Forget it, whatever.
Okay, so next song...
...I'm gonna be singing...
Are you guys still staying with me?
Don't get motion sick, okay?
Are you staying with me?
You're gonna stay with me for the next song, right?
Are you? Are you?
Okay, let's go!
Okay.
What if I just sit down?
Just like...
Okay, nyaman nih.
Okay, this is comfortable.
Aduh.
Ouch.
Ayaya.
Aya ya ya ya.
Duduk kayak begini, ya?
Sitting like this, huh?
Gimana sih? Segini aja deh.
How about this? Just this much.
Okay, ready!
To you... yes my love to you
Yes my love to you
Stay With Me / 真夜中のドア / Miki Matsubara
Stay With Me / Mayonaka no Door / Miki Matsubara
Yes my love to you
Mayonaka no Door ~stay with me
You... to you
私は私
I am me
あなたはあなたと
You are you
昨夜言ってた
What you said last night
そんな気もするわ
I feel that way too
グレーのジャケットに
In your gray jacket
見覚えがある
It looks familiar
コーヒーのしみ
The coffee stain
相変わらずなのね
You're still the same, aren't you?
ショーウィンドウに
In the show window
二人映れば
When the two of us are reflected
Stay with me
真夜中のドアを叩き
Knocking on the midnight door
帰らないでと泣いた
I cried, begging you not to go home
あの季節が 今 目の前
That season is now before my eyes
Stay with me
口ぐせを言いながら
While saying your favorite phrase
二人の瞬間を抱いて
Holding onto our moments together
まだ忘れず
I still haven't forgotten
大事にしていた
I held it dear
恋と愛とは
Love and affection
違うものだよと
Are different things, you said
昨夜言われた
You told me last night
そんな気もするわ
I feel that way too
二度目の冬が来て
A second winter came
離れていった
And drifted away
あなたの心
Your heart
振り返ればいつも
Whenever I look back
そこにあなたを
You were always there
感じていたの
I felt your presence
Stay with me
真夜中のドアを叩き
Knocking on the midnight door
心に穴があいた
A hole opened in my heart
あの季節が 今 目の前
That season is now before my eyes
Stay with me
寂しさ紛らわして
Trying to distract myself from loneliness
おいたレコードの針
The needle of the record I placed
同じメロディ
The same melody
繰り返していた
Was repeating
Stay with me
真夜中のドアを叩き
Knocking on the midnight door
帰らないでと泣いた
I cried, begging you not to go home
あの季節が 今 目の前
That season is now before my eyes
Stay with me
...Stay with me
口癖を言いながら
While saying your favorite phrase
二人の時間を抱いて
Holding our time together
まだ忘れず 暖めてた
Not yet forgotten, I was keeping it warm
Stay with me
真夜中のドアを叩き
Knocking on the midnight door
帰らないでと泣いた
And cried, "Don't go home"
あの季節が 今 目の前
That season is now before my eyes
Stay with me
口癖を言いながら
While saying your favorite phrase
二人の時間を抱いて
Holding our time together
まだ忘れず 暖めてた
Not yet forgotten, I was keeping it warm
Stay with me
真夜中のドアを叩き
Knocking on the midnight door
帰らないでと泣いた
And cried, "Don't go home"
あの季節が 今 目の前
That season is now before my eyes
Stay with me
[Cries]
Did you stay during the whole concert? Did you leave?
I saw two or three people just left.
Even though the song was called "Stay With Me",
but some people still left. Why?
Heartless! Heartless!
Human beings are so heartless.
Ampun Gusti!
Lord have mercy!
You know, this song, "Stay With Me",
I've been singing it in like unarchived karaoke,
even like I think archived karaokes back then.
I sang a lot of versions of "Stay With Me".
So this was my... chibi performance.
So I hope you guys liked that one.
Because the next one is even more...
Don't be scared.
The next one is even more sickeningly sweet.
But, but, I have a surprise because the next one...
...just like the previous song...
I forgot to mention this because I'm dumb,
but I forgot to mention that the previous song I sang was in Vestia-vision.
This song as well, I'm gonna have Vestia to come take over my...
...my body, this is my body, and sing for me.
Is that okay?
So we're gonna welcome Vestia here, okay?
Zeta!
Where are you?
Love Song / Mosawo
候補に書き出す
I start writing down candidates
感情任せの思いを綴って
Writing down thoughts left to my emotions
繰り返し消してみては
I try erasing them over and over
ありがちな台詞ばかり
But they're all just cliché lines
あなた以外は
Other than you
いらないなんて
Something like not needing anything
簡単な恋や愛だけじゃまだ
Simple love or affection still can't...
語りきれないよ
...fully express it all
愛しいだけじゃ足りないよ
Just being beloved isn't enough
歌に乗せて送りたい
I want to send my feelings in a song
息継ぎすら忘れるほどあなたを紡ぐ
Spinning words for you so much I even forget to breathe
止まらない胸の騒ぎは
This unstoppable unrest in my chest
朝を追い越したってでも
Even if it overtakes the morning, still...
でもああまだ
Still, ah, not yet
声に出せないのラブソング
It's a love song I can't put into words
いつか吐息混じりの「愛してる」を
Someday, a sigh-filled "I love you"
四小節の中
In these four bars
不細工な心　まとめられたらな
I wish I could gather up this ugly heart
打ち明けすぎないよう
So that I don't reveal too much
ちょっと下手な振りして解けた
I pretended to be a bit bad at it and it came undone
私をもっと見ていてほしい
I want you to look at me more
なんて今夜限りのメロディを
A melody for tonight only
聴いてくれたりしないかな
I wonder if you'd listen to it
だめかな
Is it no good?
数え切れないフレーズも
Countless phrases too
二度と出せない響きも
And the sounds I can never make again
伝えたいよ　起承転結はいらないから
I want to tell you, I don't need a beginning, middle, and end
何も手に付かないほど
So much that I can't focus on anything
奏でている鼓動が今ねぇ
The pulse I'm playing now, hey
また窓を曇らせていくルーム
It's fogging up the windows of the room again
ただひたすら貴方を歌うよ
I'll just keep singing about you
声を枯らして叫んだよ
I shouted until my voice was hoarse
腹が立つくらい愛
An love that almost makes me angry
吐き出しても体温だけ上がったままで
Even if I spit it out, my body temperature stays high
僕は求めたりしない
I won't ask for anything more
貴方を愛するためだけ
Just for the sake of loving you
生まれたの自信ないままの歌声
I was born with this voice, still lacking confidence
いつか綺麗に透き通る愛してるを
One day, a beautiful, transparent "I love you"
愛してるを
I love you
Waaaaa! Hehehe.
How was that?
Are you guys happy? Are you guys happy?
So we're onto the next song, which will make you guys even more happy.
Are you guys happy?
I haven't heard your voice. Hello?
Are you happy?
Senang gak?
So weird talking to myself in VR.
It's okay, I'm used to it.
Are you guys happy?
Because...
I'm the happiest.
You know what makes me so happy? Now that I think about it.
I have one thing that makes me so happy.
Pockets! Pockets!
I'm thinking, so for my next song, it's something related to happiness, I think.
Sometimes, you know, when you get too happy, you start to question yourself.
You're like, "Hmm... is it really okay for me to be this happy?"
Kayak, "Hah? Kok iya boleh ya sesenang ini?" Hah?
Like, "Huh? Is it really okay to be this happy?" Huh?
Kok iya? Senang ya?
Is that so? Happy, right?
So, I think this next song I'm gonna be wearing something... I'm gonna be wearing something that makes me happy.
Oh, wait. Don't. I know what you guys are about to say.
You guys are gonna say that I have six ears, which is not true.
It's just not true, I don't have six ears.
Okay, let me get ready. Should I go on all fours like a furry?
Guys? This?
Kayak kucing. Kayak kucing beneran nggak sih? Kayak...
Like a cat. Do I look like a real cat? Like...
Kayaknya nggak gitu deh.
I don't think so.
Kalau tampak belakang giman?
How about the back view?
Tapi norak nggak sih kalau misalnya mulai lagunya dari belakang?
But isn't it tacky if, for example, the song starts from the back?
Apa dari sini? Hmm...
Or from here? Hmm...
Apa ya deh? Entahlah.
What should I do? I don't know.
Nge-split nggak sih? Jangan jangan jangan.
Should I split? No, no, no.
Ya udah gini aja. Berdiri aja deh.
Okay, let's just do this. I'll just stand.
Okay, ready?
Okay, I'm ready!
Cho Medetai Song ~Konnani Shiawasede Iinokana?~
FRUITS ZIPPER
Super Congratulations Song ~Is it okay to be this happy?~
おめでたい！
Congratulations!
超めでたい！
Super congratulations!
中めでたい！
Moderately congratulations!
おめでたい！
Congratulations!
Cho Medetai Song ~Konnani Shiawasede Iinokana?~
Super Happy Song ~Is it okay to be this happy?~
本日ハレの日 雨でもハレ
Today is a celebratory day, even if it rains, it's sunny
一生に一度のエブリデイ だけどやっぱり今日はスペシャル
A once-in-a-lifetime everyday, but today is special after all
本日の衣装は悩みません
I won't worry about today's outfit
一周回ってまシンプル だけどアレでもやっぱ派手すぎ？
In the end, it's simple, but is it still too flashy?
来年の今は記念日 それまではたくさんもっと
Next year today will be an anniversary, until then, much more
どうでもいいことと超重要かもね
Things that don't matter and things that might be super important
そして大事なこと まずはトゥデイのぶち上げよう
And an important thing, first let's hype up today
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
私こんなに幸せでいいのかな
Is it okay for me to be this happy?
なんてホントはそのこと悩んでないけど
I say that, but I'm not actually worried about it
だってちょっとくらいのマイナスもなきゃ
Because there should be at least a little bit of negative
って思うくらいにいい感じ
It feels so good that I think that
まぁね こんなに幸せでいいので
Well, since it's okay to be this happy
だって私自分で選んだんだから
Because I chose it myself
犬は駆け回り 猫は可愛いし
Dogs run around, cats are cute
青い鳥は飛ぶ みんながいる
Bluebirds fly, everyone is here
当日はケの日 普通にいい
The day itself is an ordinary day, it's normally good
一生で一番ギャングな日 だけど仕方ないですよ
The most "gang" day of my life, but it can't be helped
って感じで冷めたりもしてるよ
I'm feeling a bit detached like that too
サプライズのメッセージ 驚くはずないでお決まり
A surprise message, I won't be surprised, it's standard
一昨年の今は他人で それまではたくさんもっと
Two years ago today we were strangers, until then, much more
無駄かも手放せないとかしあわせね
It might be pointless, but being unable to let go is happiness, isn't it?
だけど大事なこと 今は本当に大好きで
But an important thing, right now I really love it
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
あなたこんなに幸せでいいのかな
Is it okay for you to be this happy?
なんてホントはそのこと心配ないけど
I say that, but I'm not actually worried about it
だってちょっとくらいの試練もなきゃ
Because there should be at least a little bit of trial
って思うくらいにいい感じ
It feels so good that I think that
まぁね 結局幸せでいいので
Well, in the end, it's okay to be happy
だって私ちゃんと戦ったんだから
Because I fought properly
お神輿に乗って 花火も上げて
Ride the portable shrine, set off fireworks
いいことは全部一度にしよう
Let's do all the good things at once
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
私こんなに幸せでいいのかな
Is it okay for me to be this happy?
なんてホントはそのこと悩んでないけど
I say that, but I'm not actually worried about it
だってちょっとくらいのマイナスもなきゃ
Because there should be at least a little bit of negative
って思うくらいにいい感じ
It feels so good that I think that
まぁね こんなに幸せでいいので
Well, since it's okay to be this happy
だって私自分で選んだんだから
Because I chose it myself
犬は駆け回り 猫は可愛いし
Dogs run around, cats are cute
青い鳥は飛ぶ みんながいる
Bluebirds fly, everyone is here
最高の今におめでとうだよ
Congratulations to this greatest moment
Ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay...
Mic check, mic check, one, two.
Mic check, one, two, ay, ay, ay...
What's up?
DJ Seven on the house, yo!
So, next song is the rap of the night.
Actually, it's not even rap. I don't know if you guys... it's the rap of the night, for sure.
Can you... can you trust me enough if I say it's a rap song?
What if it's like a ballad? A ballad song.
Anyway, so I have a really cool song...
...and I want you guys to scream with me!
Everyone with me, okay?
Practice your screaming now. Ah! Ah, ah, ah, ah! Okay.
Okay, I want you guys to prepare your highest voice, okay?
Let's go! Let's go! I want you guys to scream as loud as you can, okay?
Because this is the last song! Wooh! Let's go!
Let's end it with a bang! Duru-ru-ru, pom-pom-pom-pom!
思い出すのは 君の歌
歌い笑う 顔が鮮明だ
どこに行ってしまったの
What I remember is your song
The face that sings and laughs is vivid
Where have you gone?
Kaijuu no Hanauta (怪獣の花唄) / Vaundy
Monster's Song / Vaundy
いつも探すんだよ
I'm always looking for it.
思い出すのは 君の歌
歌い笑う 顔が鮮明だ
君に似合うんだよ
What I remember is your song
The face that sings and laughs is vivid
It suits you well.
ずっと見ていたいよ
I want to watch you forever.
でも最後に 見たいのは
きっともう 君の夢の中
もう一度
But in the end, what I want to see
Is probably already in your dreams
Once more
また聴かせてくれよ
聴きたいんだ
Please let me hear it again
I want to hear it
もっと騒げ怪獣の歌
まだ消えない 夢の歌となれ
Make more noise, monster's song
The dream song that hasn't faded away yet, become the song
君がいつも 歌う怪獣の歌
まだ消えない 口ずさんでしまうよ
The monster's song you always sing
I end up humming it, it hasn't faded yet
思い出すのは 君がいた
ギター持てる 君がいた
What I remember is that you were there
You were there with a guitar
忘れられないんだよ
だったら僕が歌うよ
I can't forget
If that's the case, I'll sing
でも最後に 見たいのは
きっともう 君の夢の中
もう一度
But in the end, what I want to see
Is probably already in your dreams
Once more
また聴かせてくれよ
聴きたいんだ
Please let me hear it again
I want to hear it
もっと騒げ怪獣の歌
まだ消えない 夢の歌となれ
Make more noise, monster's song
The dream song that hasn't faded away yet, become the song
君がいつも 歌う怪獣の歌
まだ消えない 口ずさんでしまうよ
The monster's song you always sing
I end up humming it, it hasn't faded yet
落ちていく 過去は鮮明で
見せたい 未来は繊細で
The falling past is vivid
The future I want to show is delicate
過ぎていく 日々には鈍感な君へ
To you, who are insensitive to the passing days
落ちていく 過去は鮮明で
見せたい 未来は繊細で
The falling past is vivid
The future I want to show is delicate
過ぎていく 日々には鈍感な君へ
To you, who are insensitive to the passing days
ねぇ もっと騒げ怪獣の歌
まだ消えない 夢の歌となれ
Hey, make more noise, monster's song
The dream song that hasn't faded away yet, become the song
君がいつも 歌う怪獣の歌
まだ消えない 口ずさんでしまうよ
The monster's song you always sing
I end up humming it, it hasn't faded yet
眠れない 夜に 手を伸ばして
Stretching out hands into the sleepless night
眠れない 夜に また伸ばして
Stretching out hands again into the sleepless night
そんな日々でいたいのに
Even though I want to stay in such days
懲りずに 手を伸ばして
Without learning, stretching out hands
眠れない 夜に また伸ばして
そんな夜に 歌う怪獣の歌
Stretching out hands again into the sleepless night
The monster's song sung on such a night
Yay! How was it? Did you guys enjoy the performance?
Hehe, fantastic side eye in this. I hope you guys liked it!
I enjoyed it as well! I've always wanted to do a mini-live,
so it's a dream come true that I get to do a mini-live for you.
And, uh, I have Basil with me, I have you guys with me,
although you guys are behind those screens in front of me, it's okay.
Uh, I had so much fun! Thank you for staying with me for the past two years!
...um, here's to...
...hopefully many, many years in the future, you know?
Many, many more.
Okay?
Aku peres kalian sampai habis.
I'll squeeze you all until there's nothing left.
Jasad kalian.
Your corpses.
Jadi, hari ini kita berhenti di sini.
So, we'll stop here for today.
今日は終わりたいと思うんですけど...
I'd like to end it today, but...
But, but but but but but but but but...
Not before...
Not before I do something...
...which is...